// subtraction.js
export const subtractionQuestions = [
    { id: 1, question: "10 - 4 = ?", correctAnswer: 6, options: [5, 6, 7, 8], operation: "subtraction" },
    { id: 2, question: "15 - 7 = ?", correctAnswer: 8, options: [7, 8, 9, 10], operation: "subtraction" },
    { id: 3, question: "20 - 5 = ?", correctAnswer: 15, options: [14, 15, 16, 17], operation: "subtraction" },
    { id: 4, question: "9 - 3 = ?", correctAnswer: 6, options: [5, 6, 7, 8], operation: "subtraction" },
    { id: 5, question: "12 - 6 = ?", correctAnswer: 6, options: [5, 6, 7, 8], operation: "subtraction" },
    { id: 6, question: "18 - 9 = ?", correctAnswer: 9, options: [8, 9, 10, 11], operation: "subtraction" },
    { id: 7, question: "14 - 5 = ?", correctAnswer: 9, options: [8, 9, 10, 11], operation: "subtraction" },
    { id: 8, question: "16 - 8 = ?", correctAnswer: 8, options: [7, 8, 9, 10], operation: "subtraction" },
    { id: 9, question: "13 - 4 = ?", correctAnswer: 9, options: [8, 9, 10, 11], operation: "subtraction" },
    { id: 10, question: "11 - 2 = ?", correctAnswer: 9, options: [8, 9, 10, 11], operation: "subtraction" }
  ];
  